Guide to J. Hugo Aronson papers 1924-1968
Montana Historical Society Research Center
J. Hugo Aronson papers
1924-1968
Montana Historical Society, Research Center Archives Archives 225 N. Roberts PO Box 201201 Helena MT 59620-1201 (406) 444-2681 MHSlibrary@mt.gov
MC 338
Aronson, J. Hugo (John Hugo), 1891-1978
18 linear feet of shelf space
J. Hugo Aronson was governor of Montana (1953-1961) and served in Montana House of Representatives (1938-1944) and the Montana State Senate (1944-1952). The bulk of the collection consists of campaign/political materials, correspondence, speeches, press releases, subject files, reports, and scrapbooks concerning his two terms as governor. The collection also contains J. Hugo Aronson’s business and personal papers including financial documents, correspondence and subject material.
Biographical Note
J. Hugo Aronson was born in Gallstad, Sweden on September 1, 1891, a son of Aron Johanson (1856-1927), a tenant farmer, and Rika Ryding Johannsen (1857-1940). The Johannsens had five children: Anna, Karl, Julia, John Hugo, and Erik Johannsen Aronson. Anna Aronson married Karl Skold and the couple had three children: Gunnar, Karin, and Allan. Julia Aronson Joseffson had two sons. Sven Johanson was also a nephew of J. Hugo Aronson.
J. Hugo Aronson was educated in the public schools of Gallstad, Sweden. He left school at the age of 14 to work. Hugo came to the United States from Sweden in 1911, penniless, except for the $25.00 immigration fee required. His brothers and sisters remained residents of Sweden. After working at various jobs through thirty-eight states, Hugo arrived in Columbus, Montana in 1914. While working for Frank Young in Columbus he got the nickname "The Galloping Swede." In 1915 Hugo filed for a 320-acre homestead in Elk Basin.
On December 8, 1917, he enlisted in the U.S. Army at Billings and served as a private with the 20th Engineers in France. On June 3, 1919, while in France with the American Expeditionary Forces, Aronson married Matilda Langane, who was in charge of the French-American Red Cross group and had been one of premier Georges Clemenceau’s secretaries. He was honorably discharged on July 17, 1919, as a private first class at Hoboken, New Jersey.
Aronson returned to Columbus with his wife and rented a farm which he operated while working in the oil fields at Elk Basin, Wyoming. In January 1923, Hugo went to Sunburst, Montana where he was a tool dresser, or driller’s helper, for a drilling company. In 1924, another rig-builder, Roy Berrey, and Hugo became partners in the Sunburst Construction Company. It was a profitable business but only after a year Roy decided to sell Hugo out. Hugo then operated his own rig-building outfit under his own name and started advertising as "The Galloping Swede." Matilda was the bookkeeper. He added a trucking business to the rig-building company, and at the time Hugo was the largest rig-builder in Montana. When oil was discovered in Kevin-Sunburst fields in Montana, Hugo built the first building in Oilmont. In 1928 he founded Gallop City near Conrad. It was the largest of the oil-fields camps, a community which boasted 500 inhabitants.
Hugo and Matilda Aronson traveled to Sweden and France to visit family in 1924. That same year, they traveled to Glacier National Park and Waterton. They also visited California, Nevada, and Utah.
Matilda died in Paris, France in 1936 of cancer.
On September 25, 1944, J. Hugo Aronson married Rose McClure in Minneapolis, Minnesota. Rose McClure Aronson was born in Mondovi, Washington in 1904, the daughter of rancher Evan McClure and Bertha Brink McClure. An educator, she was superintendent of schools in Glacier County at the time of her marriage. The Aronsons had one daughter, Rika Berthevan Aronson, who was born in Cut Bank on December 13, 1945. She married Gary Robert Mogolis and the couple had two children: Joani Michele (born Oct. 1, 1967) and John Robert.
Aronson's political career began with his election as Cut Bank City Alderman in 1934. A Republican, he served three terms in the Montana House of Representatives as a member from Glacier County (1939-1944), and for the next eight years was a member of the Montana State Senate, also representing Glacier County. Aronson served on the board of directors of the Montana Motor Transport Association for many years. He was also a member of the Veterans of Foreign Wars (V.F.W.) and the American Legion. He was a member of the Algeria Temple, Ancient Arabic Order of Nobles of the Mystic Shrine, Blue Lodge, York Rite, and Scottish Rite Masonic bodies.
J. Hugo Aronson was elected governor of Montana on November 4, 1952. George Gosman was elected lieutenant governor. Other executive officers included Attorney General Arnold Olsen, Secretary of State Sam W. Mitchell, and Superintendent of Public Instruction Mary M. Condon. Hugh Adair was the Chief Justice of the Supreme Court of Montana; Alex Stephenson, Chief of the Highway Patrol; and Wesley Castles was Aronson's executive secretary.
Aronson was elected to a second term in 1956. Democrat Paul Cannon was elected lieutenant governor. Edna J. Hinman served as Clerk of the Supreme Court; Forrest H. Anderson as Attorney General; Harriett Miller as Superintendent of Public Instruction; and S.H. Mitchell was the Adjutant General.
As Governor, Hugo battled over oil and gas leasing that arose out of the discovery of oil in the Williston Basin in 1951; he worked for better schools, for prisoner rehabilitation, for oil conservation, and for highway development. In 1959, a new governors' residence was built and the Aronsons became the first family to reside there.
Following his second term as governor, the Aronsons retired to Bigfork, Montana. Rose Aronson died February 25, 1968 and J. Hugo Aronson's death came on the tenth anniversary of his wife's, February 25, 1978, at the age of 86.
J. Hugo Aronson papers consist of documents relating to the life and career of the former governor.
Series 1-2: These series contain the personal files of J. Hugo Aronson and his family. These files contain biographical material of J. Hugo Aronson, Matilda Lengagne Aronson, and Rose McClure Aronson; correspondence to and from Rose, Rika, and J. Hugo Aronson including condolence letters to J. Hugo for the death of his first wife, Matilda, reaction towards the articles "What America Means to Me" and "Montana's Galloping Swede," and Christmas letters from 1961. The series also includes financial statements and balance sheets for C. A. F. Oil Co., A. E. Crumley, and Hagerty Oil Co., M. H. O. Co., and legal documents including contracts with the Northern Pacific Railroad for the transportation of livestock, the United States for construction of water storage facility, and oil and gas leases.
Series 3-4: These small series contains material from J. Hugo's time in the Montana House of Representative and the Senate. The series contain subject files on the sale of State owned lots in Glacier County and conscientious objection and the First Methodist Church during the Korean War.
Series 5: Campaign materials consist of campaign letters from Aronson for Governor Club, campaign speeches, subject files focusing on campaign issues including oil and gas lease program for schools and Montana highway program. The series also contain John Bonner and Arnold Olsen’s campaign speeches when they ran against J. Hugo.
Series 6: The bulk of this series documents J. Hugo’s governorship. Much of the correspondences in this series are congratulatory of election and reelection victories with little information on policy and strategy. Speeches include dedications; the Governors message to the Legislature for 1955, 1957, 1959; keynote addresses to Montana Republican Convention; and to the Montana AFL-CIO, Montana Press Association, panel on Natural resources, stockgrowers, United States Senate on Interior and Insular Affairs, and the woolgrowers. The series also contains subject files on various state agencies including but not limited to the Highway Commission, Highway Patrol, State Board of Education, State Board of Examiners, and State Board of Land Commissioners. Scrapbooks, which date from 1952-1961 and specifically focus on his governorship.
Arranged by subgroup and series
Collection is open for research
Acquisition information available upon request.
Artifacts, photographs, and printed materials have been separated to the Museum, Photo Archives, and Library respectively.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the Montana Historical Society catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search under these terms.
Montana. Office of the Governor.; Republican Party (Mont.)
Elections--Montana.; Governors--Montana.
Montana--Politics and government.; Montana--Politics and government--20th century.
Montana.; Government and Politics.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- J. Hugo Aronson
  - Biographical Material
    - Biographical writings, undated (Box-folder 1 / 1)
  - Correspondence Incoming
    - Personal: Condolences for the Death of Matilda Aronson, 1936 (Box-folder 1 / 2)
    - Personal: Get Well Wishes, 1967 (Box-folder 1 / 3)
    - Personal: Miscellaneous (regarding employee recommendation; Matilda's health; birthday wishes; Republican Convention), 1923-1951, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 1 / 4)
    - Personal: Miscellaneous (Swedish), 1941, 1949-1961 (Box-folder 1 / 5)
  - Correspondence General
    - Business: re Land owned by Beatrice Sartell and Matilda and J. Hugo Aronson, 1926-1939 (Box-folder 1 / 6)
    - Business: A-M (correspondents include J. Hugo Aronson; H. B. Burleson; Maxine Kenyon; J. E. Manning), 1942-1943 (Box-folder 1 / 7)
    - Business: Bills and Statements (correspondents include J. Hugo Aronson; H. B. Burleson; Claude Carbis; George Simpson), 1942 (Box-folder 1 / 8)
    - Business: A-S (correspondents include J. Hugo Aronson; H. B. Burleson; Claude Carbis; George Simpson), 1943-1945 (Box-folder 1 / 9)
    - Personal: American Magazine Article, "What America Means to Me", 1956-1958 (Box-folder 1 / 10)
    - Personal: Saturday Evening Post Article, "Montana's Galloping Swede", 1957-1958 (Box-folder 1 / 11)
  - Financial Documents
    - Business: Balance Sheets (C. A. F. Oil Co.; A. E. Crumley; and Hagerty Oil Co.), 1946-1947, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1 / 12)
    - Business: Bills (Trucking Contractor), 1941-1944 (Box-folder 1 / 13)
    - Business: Financial Summaries for Oil Drilling on Blackfeet Land (A. E. Crumley), 1943-1948 (Box-folder 2 / 1)
    - Business: Financial Summaries for Oil Drilling on Blackfeet Land (Hagerty Oil Co.), 1943-1953 (Box-folder 2 / 2)
    - Business: Payroll [includes oversize material: see OVBX 6], 1942 (Box-folder 2 / 3)
    - Business: Statements (C. C. Operating Co.), 1928-1936 (Box-folder 2 / 4)
    - Business: Statements (Land owned by Beatrice Sartell and Matilda and J. Hugo Aronson), 1935-1940 (Box-folder 2 / 5)
    - Business: Statements (M. H. O. Oil Co.), 1941-1945 (Box-folder 2 / 6)
    - Business: Statements (Trucking Contractor), 1942-1943 (Box-folder 2 / 7-8)
    - Business: Statements (Grace Hagerty), 1944-1948 (Box-folder 2 / 9)
    - Business: Statements (M. H. O. Oil Co.), 1946-1956 (Box-folder 2 / 10)
    - Business: Statements (C. A. F. Oil Co.), 1952-1956 (Box-folder 2 / 11)
    - Business: Statements (Hagerty Oil Co.), 1953-1956 (Box-folder 2 / 12)
    - Personal: Receipts for Hospital Treatments and the Funeral for Matilda Aronson (French), 1936 (Box-folder 2 / 13)
    - Personal: Receipts (Swedish and French), 1936, 1941, 1949 (Box-folder 2 / 14)
    - Personal: Receipts (Sampled), 1953-1955 (Box-folder 2 / 15)
    - Personal: Statements (Conrad Mercantile Company), 1936 (Box-folder 2 / 16)
  - Legal Documents
    - Business: Agreement with H. B. Burleson to transport material from Benbow Mill, Montana to Columbus, Montana, 1942 (Box-folder 3 / 1)
    - Business: Contract with Northern Pacific Railway transportation of Livestock, 1941 (Box-folder 3 / 2)
    - Business: Contract with United States of America for Construction of Water Storage Facility, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3 / 3)
    - Business: Oil and Gas Leases, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 3 / 4)
    - Personal: United States Immigration and Travel Documents (includes Casper Stahl and Lucien and Renee Lengagne), 1923, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 3 / 5)
  - Organizational Records
    - Business: Hagerty Oil Company Meeting Minutes, 1954 (Box-folder 3 / 6)
  - Subject Files
    - Business: Construction of Water Storage Facility (including correspondence), 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3 / 7)
    - Business: Elkhorn Metals, Inc., 1937-1938 (Box-folder 3 / 8)
    - Personal: Swedish Bank (including correspondence), 1929-1940 (Box-folder 3 / 9)
    - Personal: Westminster Foreign Bank (including correspondence), 1929-1948 (Box-folder 3 / 10)
  - Miscellany
    - Business: Driver's Daily Log, 1942 (Box-folder 3 / 11)
    - Personal: Awards and Certificates [includes oversize material: see OVBX 6], 1962, 1964, undated (Box-folder 3 / 12)
    - Personal: Building Permit for Home in Cut Bank, Montana, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 3 / 13)
    - Personal: Signed Copy the Saturday Evening Post, December 7, 1957 (Box-folder OVBX / 6)
    - Personal: Miscellaneous, 1932, 1937, 1940, undated (Box-folder 3 / 14)
- Aronson Family
  - Biographical Material
    - Miscellaneous, Matilda Lengagne Aronson (includes French Passport, identity book, travel documents, death notice), 1919, 1924, 1936, undated (Box-folder 3 / 15)
    - Miscellaneous, Rose McClure Aronson (includes clippings, measurement chart, notes), 1959, undated (Box-folder 3 / 16)
  - Correspondence Incoming
    - Christmas Cards, 1961 (Box-folder 3 / 17-18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1954 (Box-folder 3 / 19)
  - Legal Documents
    - Passports (Hugo, Rika, and Rose), 1919, 1928, 1949 (Box-folder 3 / 20)
  - Miscellany
    - Address Book, Rose Aronson, undated (Box-folder 3 / 21)
- House of Representatives
  - Subject Files
    - Sale of State Owned Lots in Glacier County, 1939, 1941 (Box-folder 3 / 22)
- Senate
  - Correspondence Incoming
    - Fred Ward, Meagher County News, undated (Box-folder 3 / 23)
  - Subject Files
    - Conscientious Objectors and the First Methodist Church, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 3 / 24)
- Campaign for Governor
  - Correspondence General
    - A (correspondents include Arne Anzjon, Montana Broadcasting; Argus-Farmer Newspaper), 1952 (Box-folder 3 / 25)
    - Aronson for Governor Club (includes correspondence to and from Frank Connelly, Treasurer; D. E. Hageman, Secretary; Fred Martin, Campaign Manager), 1952 (Box-folder 4 / 1-2)
    - B (correspondents include Vic Benson, Covered Wagon Ranch; M. W. Blankenship, Missoula County Republican Headquarters; Robert Burroughs, Eisenhower for President Headquarters; Ken Byerly, Byerly Publishing Co.), 1952 (Box-folder 4 / 3)
    - C (correspondents include Ed Craney, Pacific Northwest Broadcasters; William Cherry; Cremer Rodeo Land and Livestock Co.), 1952 (Box-folder 4 / 4)
    - D-G (correspondents include Harry Duntsch, Bozeman Courier; J. G. Edmiston, President Conrad National Bank of Kalispell; Ward Fanning, Jr., Chairman Ballot Battalion Forum; Roswell Goodman, Chairman Lewis and Clark County Young Republicans), 1952 (Box-folder 4 / 5)
    - H (correspondents include Grace Hanson, President Kalispell Business and Professional Women's Club; Hazel Hitchcock, Republican Headquarters; John Hoyt, Toole Co. Attorney), 1952 (Box-folder 4 / 6)
    - I-M (correspondents include Alma Jacobs, Montana State Federation of Colored Women's Clubs; Liberty County Times; Peggy McCormick, Eastern Montana College of Education; Meagher County News; Walter Mecklenburg), 1952 (Box-folder 4 / 7)
    - N-R (correspondents include Bill Neary, Miner's Union Legislative Committee; Northwest Tribune; Don Nutter; Joseph Oien; W. E. Pierce, Chairman Republican County Central Committee; Junior Reinemer, Chairman Aronson Committee; Republican State Central Committee), 1952 (Box-folder 4 / 8)
    - S (correspondents include Frances Sanborn, Chairman Montana Republican Women's Clubs; Lyle Standish, Chairman Teton County Aronson for Governor Club; Sid Stewart, Senator Deer Lodge County; Ruby Swanson, Mountain View Lodge), 1952 (Box-folder 5 / 1)
    - T-Y (correspondents include Frank Trippet, Montana D. A. V. News; Don Valiton, Senator Powell County; T. B. Van Horn, Finance Chairman Republican Central Committee; C. M. Wall, President Montana Chamber of Commerce; Herb Watts, Havre Daily News), 1952 (Box-folder 5 / 2)
    - Aronson for Governor Club (includes correspondence to and from Wesley Castles, Secretary; James Felt, Chairman; Ashton Jones, Campaign Manager), 1956 (Box-folder 5 / 3)
    - Campaign(correspondents include KGHL-Billings; Lions Club; Montana D. A. V. News; Montana Farm Bureau Federation; Montana Legionnaire; Republican Central Committee; Women's Republican Club), 1956 (Box-folder 5 / 4-5)
    - Campaign Contributions, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 5 / 6-7)
    - Ford-Gainan Advertising Agency, 1956 (Box-folder 5 / 8)
    - Little People for an Honest Governor, 1956 (Box-folder 5 / 9)
  - Financial
    - Bills (General Election), 1952 (Box-folder 5 / 10)
    - Receipt Log [includes oversize material: see OVBX 6], 1952 (Box-folder 5 / 11)
    - Basic Budget Plan, 1956 (Box-folder 5 / 12)
    - Receipts, Ford-Gainan Advertising Agency, 1956 (Box-folder 6 / 1)
    - Press Releases
    - Reelection Campaign, 1956 (Box-folder 6 / 2)
  - Printed Material
    - "They Shall Know the Truth and the Truth Shall Make Them Angry", 1952, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6 / 3)
  - Speeches
    - Speeches by others (includes two untitled speeches by Albert Krause and Senator Liggetts), 1952 (Box-folder 6 / 4)
    - "To Every Montana Voter", 1952 (Box-folder 1 / 5)
    - Campaign Speeches (re accomplishments of Governor Aronson's Administration, Cochrane Dam dedication, Farm Program, "How to Smear a Legislator", Montana Employment Service, Montana Oil-Lease Program for Schools, Montana's Economic Outlook, Need for Equalization, Policy Speech, Rebuttal to Arnold Olsen’s Campaign), 1956 (Box-folder 6 / 6)
  - Subject Files
    - Campaign for Governor (includes campaign song, correspondence, flyers) [includes oversize material: see OVBX 6], 1952 (Box-folder 6 / 7)
    - Daily Itinerary, 1952 (Box-folder 6 / 8)
    - Radio Advertisements, 1952 (Box-folder 6 / 9)
    - Small Trailer Tax, 1952 (Box-folder 6 / 10)
    - Campaign Research Material, 1955-1956, undated (Box-folder 6 / 11)
    - Itinerary (includes correspondence), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6 / 12)
    - Montana County Republican Chairmen (includes contact list) [includes oversize material: see OVBX 6], 1956 (Box-folder 6 / 13)
    - Montana Highway Program, 1956 (Box-folder 6 / 14)
    - Montana Opinion Questionnaire, 1956 (Box-folder 6 / 15)
    - Montana Press Association, 1956 (Box-folder 6 / 16)
    - Oil and Gas Lease Program for Schools, 1955-1956, undated (Box-folder 6 / 17)
    - Arnold Olsen for Governor, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6 / 18)
    - Reelection Campaign for Governor (includes correspondence, flyers, clippings), 1956 (Box-folder 6 / 19)
    - Republican State Central Committee (includes platforms, resolutions, and correspondence), 1956, 1958 (Box-folder 6 / 20)
  - Miscellany
    - Mailing Lists, 1952 (Box-folder 7 / 1)
    - Voter Registration Lists (includes Garfield County; Lennep, Rock Creek and Ringling Precincts), 1952 (Box-folder 7 / 2)
    - John Bonner: Speeches (includes speeches regarding Utility Rates, Oil, Labor, State Institutions, and Workmen's Compensation), 1956 (Box-folder 7 / 3)
    - Arnold Olsen: Speeches (includes speeches regarding Oil and Utility Rates, Oil Leasing, Freight Rates and Oil and Gas Leases), 1953-1956 (Box-folder 7 / 4)
    - Arnold Olsen: Speeches (includes speeches regarding Federal Aid and Education, Right-to-Work Law, Slot Machines and Gambling, and Workmen's Compensation), 1956 (Box-folder 7 / 5)
- Governor
  - Correspondence Incoming
    - Congratulations on Election: Telegrams, 1952 (Box-folder 7 / 6)
    - Albert C. Johnson, 1952 (Box-folder 7 / 7)
    - Thure H. Peterson, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 7 / 8)
    - Thank You Letters, Governors' Conference, 1960 (Box-folder 7 / 9)
    - Robert Yellowtail Newsletters, undated (Box-folder 7 / 10)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 7 / 11)
  - Correspondence General
    - A (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include American Legion; L. J. Anders, Broadwater County Representative; Carl Anderson; A. L. (Roy) Atkinson, Lake County Representative; Arlo Axelson, Silver Bow County Republican Planning Committee), 1952 (Box-folder 7 / 12)
    - Appointments: Attorney; State Boards and Agencies, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 7 / 13)
    - Appointments: Board of Education, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 7 / 14)
    - Appointments: Custodian, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 7 / 15)
    - Appointments: Department of Agriculture, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 7 / 16)
    - Appointments: Fish and Game, 1952 (Box-folder 7 / 17)
    - Appointments: Highway Commission, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 8 / 1)
    - Appointments: Highway Department, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 8 / 2)
    - Appointments: Highway Patrol, 1952 (Box-folder 8 / 3)
    - Appointments: Home for the Aged, Lewistown, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 8 / 4)
    - Appointments: Industrial Accident Board, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 8 / 5)
    - Appointments: Industrial School, Miles City, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 8 / 6)
    - Appointments: Livestock Commission, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 8 / 7)
    - Appointments: Motor Vehicle Office, 1952 (Box-folder 8 / 8)
    - Appointments: Public Health Board, 1952 (Box-folder 8 / 9)
    - Appointments: Public Welfare, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 8 / 10)
    - Appointments: Public Welfare, Child Welfare Division, 1952 (Box-folder 8 / 11)
    - Appointments: Purchasing Department, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 8 / 12)
    - Appointments: State Hospital, Warm Springs, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 8 / 13)
    - Appointments: State Prison, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 8 / 14)
    - Appointments: Water Conservation Board, 1952 (Box-folder 8 / 15)
    - B (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include O. A. Bergeson; Big Horn County State Bank; Thomas Briggs, President of Welcome Wagon, Inc,; Ken Byerly, President of Byerly Publishing Co.; Ed Byrne; L. W. Busch, Senator Fallon County), 1952 (Box-folder 8 / 16)
    - C (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include Chandler Cohagen, Architect; E. E. Collins, Administrator Rocky Mountain College; Elizabeth Connelly, President of Montana Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs; Harry Cooley, Northern School Supply Co.; Ed Cooney, President of Montana Radio Stations, Inc.; W. J. Cooney; Clarence Cunningham, Hold Firm the American Way), 1952 (Box-folder 8 / 17)
    - D (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include M. S. Danklefsen, Mayor of Jordon, Montana; Tom J. Davis, Attorney; M. D. Dennis, The Texas Company; Wesley D'Ewart, Montana Congressman; G. P. Drowley, President of the First National Bank; Howard R. Dove), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 1)
    - E (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include Charles F. Eastabrooks, Manager Monmouth Branch of the United States National Bank; Graydon Edwards; Andrew Eggenberger; Dwight D. Eisenhower; E. P. Ekegren; Lula M. Eschle, Butte City Librarian; Troy Evans, Senator Silver Bow County), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 2)
    - F (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include Clyde Flint, Hotel Havre; G. H. Flint, American Insurance Company; Larry Florek, Union Construction Company, Inc.; John Fouse; E. R. Fortin, Agent Great Northern Railway Co.), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 3)